cellphonedigest.net 2013-10-05

# Privacy Policy - Cell Phone Digest

  | 

## Cell Phone Digest - cellstores 

Thank you for visiting Cell Phone Digest, a website of Cell Phone Digest - cellstores, Inc. (“Cell Phone Digest - cellstores”). Cell Phone Digest - cellstores knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Cell Phone Digest, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice. Cell Phone Digest - cellstores is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitor's personally identifiable information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is used at our site. 

Cell Phone Digest - cellstores is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, non-profit organization whose mission is to build users' trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This covers the site www.Cell Phone Digest. Because this web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, Cell Phone Digest - cellstores has agreed to notify you of: 

  * What personally identifiable information of yours or third party personally identifiable information that is collected from you through the web site. 

  * The organization collecting the information.

  * How the information is used.

  * With whom the information may be shared.

  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information. 

  * The kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under Cell Phone Digest - cellstores control.

  * How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, or complaints arising from our use of your personal information, please contact our Customer Service department via certified mail to Cell Phone Digest - cellstores, Inc., 1010 Wisconsin Avenue, Suite 600, Washington, DC 20007. You also may send your request via e-mail to Customer Relations. If you do not receive acknowledgment of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should then contact TRUSTe through the "TRUSTe WatchDog Dispute Resolution Process.” TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with the Web site to resolve your concerns or complaints.

**Site Technology**

As with many Web sites, we may use "cookies" and/or other technology (e.g., web bugs, e-mail bugs, clear GIFs, web beacons and tracker GIFs) in the Site or in our communications with you to enhance the functionality of the Site and to make your transactions and other activities more convenient and efficient (collectively, "Tracking Technologies"). These technologies may vary, but in some cases may involve a small file stored locally on the computer used to access the Site, and may be used by us to store and collect information relating to your viewing and use of the Site and our correspondences with you. You may set your web browser software not to accept cookies, but, if so, certain functionality of the Site may be affected. We may collect your IP (Internet Protocol) address to help diagnose problems with our server, administer our Site and identify our users. We may also use such technologies to remember user preferences or minimize the need for you to re-enter information.

Third parties (including, but not limited to, software vendors, advertisers and fulfillment companies) may also use Tracking Technologies by or through the Site. We have no control over what information such third parties track or collect, and we have no responsibility or liability for any tracking, data collection or other activities of such third parties.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the[ advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [ opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).) 

## What Information We Collect and How We Use It

### Personally Identifiable Information

When you place an order for products or services we collect certain types of personally identifiable information required to fulfill those products or services, including (1) contact information, such as name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number; (2) payment information, such as credit card number, or (3) ID verification information, such as credit card number, date of birth, Social Security Number, or Driver's License Number, as may be required by a wireless carrier if you are requesting a new account.

We use this information to process requests for products and services. For those customers applying for new wireless service activation, this includes performing a standard industry credit check by inputting your data into the wireless carrier's system. Once the carrier runs the check, it informs us of an applicant's approval status so that we can either process the order or notify those applicants who have not been approved of their status. Aside from approval status information, we do not have access to an applicant's credit-history information.

We also use collected information to communicate with you, such as to notify you about updates to products, to send you order confirmations, or to provide you with important product warranty or safety information. Your e-mail address may also be sent a third party newsletter from WireOffers.com. You can easily opt out of this newsletter by visiting wireoffers.com or by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any of these e-mails. In addition, we use contact information you provide to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, and to offer you, by means of e-mail or through our newsletter, additional products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

Information from IP addresses is used for system administration, to examine overall traffic trends, troubleshooting, etc. This information is used only in the aggregate form. IP addresses are not linked to any personally identifiable information, meaning the user session is tracked, but the user is anonymous. 

### Supplementation of Information 

We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect online with outside records (e.g., information from our Strategic Partners or from wireless providers) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. 

### Sharing of Your Information 

Agents and contractors who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect it in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice.

To fulfill your requests for products and services, we may need to share some of your personally identifiable information with both the wireless provider from which you would like to request service and the "Strategic Partner” through which you accessed Cell Phone Digest - cellstores, or with other affiliates or co-branding partners.

More specifically, when you place an order for wireless services, we will share names, contact information, and other information that is necessary for the wireless carrier to provide you with its services, and to provide you with products that we think you will find interesting. The provider may use this information for credit approval, service activation, and from time to time, for its own marketing purposes. You should consult the wireless providers' respective privacy policies, as this Notice does not cover their use of your information. 

In addition, if you access Cell Phone Digest - cellstores through a third-party site, such as one of our Strategic Partners' sites, we also may need to report certain personally identifiable information (e.g., name and e-mail address) back to that Web site. As we explain further below in the section that follows, we will tell you at the point of collection if we will share personally identifiable information with the Strategic Partner through which you access the Cell Phone Digest - cellstores service. 

In addition, we may share aggregated demographic information with our Strategic Partners, wireless providers and advertisers.

### Sharing of Affiliate Information in the Affiliate Sign-Up Process 

Information submitted by potential Affiliates in the Affiliate Sign-Up Process is submitted to Linkshare. Linkshare's privacy policy can be found here: www.linkshare.com.

### Our Collection of Personally Identifiable Information Through a Third-party Web Site

To provide you with content and service, we have relationships with many of the best service and content companies. As a result of these relationships, you can access Cell Phone Digest - cellstores through a third-party Web site. You can recognize most of the Cell Phone Digest - cellstores pages on these third-party sites by looking for the joint branding of Cell Phone Digest - cellstores and a third-party company. For example, if you see a logo on the page that says "Powered by Cell Phone Digest - cellstores," you are on a co-branded page.

Whenever you provide registration information on a co-branded page, that data may be shared with the third-party site through which you access Cell Phone Digest - cellstores. We may share personally identifiable information with third parties. By agreeing to this privacy policy, you give us permission to transfer your personal information to third parties for the purposes of analyzing it to make your experience better and offering products to you. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of such third parties, as this Notice does not cover their use of information.

### Third Party Sharing of Information

Cell Phone Digest - cellstores sometimes may offer content (e.g., promotions, affiliations, sponsorships) that is sponsored by or cobranded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity.

### Live Help Function

To better serve you and respond to your questions regarding our products or services, we also maintain a Live Help function through which we can respond, in real time, to your questions about our products and services. This information enables us to understand the types of questions our users have about our products and services so that we may continue to improve our content and offerings. 

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information 

We may collect certain non-personally identifiable information about our visitors when you visit many of our Web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Netscape, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows '98 or Mac OS) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., America Online, Earthlink).

We use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our service pages and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze service usage. 

### Legal Process/Disclaimer 

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process or when we believe in good faith that the law requires it, for example, in response to a court order, subpoena or a law enforcement agency's request. 

## Choices/Opt Out

If you prefer not to receive marketing information, including emails from us, or wish to fully deactivate your account information from us, simply let us know by sending a letter via certified mail to Cell Phone Digest - cellstores, Inc., 1010 Wisconsin Avenue, Suite 600, Washington, DC 20007 or an e-mail to Customer Relations or by visiting www.WireOffers.com. Please note that even if you chose to opt out of Cell Phone Digest - cellstores's marketing, we will continue to send you important service-related communications (e.g., order confirmation or product safety information). However, these are not promotional in nature.

### Cookies

To enhance your experience with our site, we use "cookies." Cookies are used by your computer's browser to store your preferences. We use both session and persistent cookies. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites.

### Tracking Pixels

Tracking pixels are used to track total orders for select partners.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. If you set your browser not to accept cookies, you will still be able to use our site.

This site makes use of a technology designed to enhance your browsing experience. The technology, provided as a hosted service application by Fireclick ®, makes use of a small and transparent Java applet to provide you with a faster browsing experience. In addition, aggregate reporting information is collected and made available to the site owner only. No personal or personally identifiable information is gathered or used for this process. If for any reason you do not wish to have this technology enabled while browsing this site, please click here. A cookie will be set on your browser that instructs the service not to start. If you have disabled the service and wish to reactivate it, please click here. Additional information on Fireclick's technology may be found at www.fireclick.com.

### Links

In addition, our site contains links to other Web sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Our privacy policy does not cover these third parties' use of information. Visitors should consult the other companies' and sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

## Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online. 

All information submitted is protected by our secure server, which automatically encrypts your personally identifiable information so that it cannot be read while traveling over the Internet.

## Reviewing Your Information

If you would like to review and update or correct the personally identifiable information that we have collected from you online, or if no longer wish to continue your service with us, simply send your request via certified mail to Cell Phone Digest - cellstores, Inc., 1010 Wisconsin Avenue, Suite 600, Washington, DC 20007. You may also send your request via e-mail to Customer Relations. 

To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this statement, or would like more information on our privacy practices, please [contact us](http://www.cellphonedigest.net/Contact_Us_form.php). 

## Updates and Notification of Changes

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it. If we make any material changes in our privacy practices that do not affect user information already stored in our database, we will post a prominent notice on our web site notifying users of the change.
